Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Director, Institute of Politics, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, 1987-1988; XII.
  - Events, 6.
    - Idaho Republican Party Lincoln Day Dinner, Boise, ID, February 11, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 12)
    - International Institute of Women Political Leaders Organizational Conference, Reception and Dinner, Cambridge, MA, March 24, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 13)
    - International Organ Transplant Forum, Honorary Committee, Pittsburgh, PA, September 8-11, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Health Policy Analysis, Interview, Cambridge, MA, November 20, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 15)
    - Ivy League Schools Public Relations Officers, Luncheon, Cambridge, MA, June 24, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 16)
    - Janeway, Michael, former IOP student, Lunch, Cambridge, MA, ca. September 25, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 17)
    - January Group, Breakfast, New York, NY, September 10, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 18)
    - Japanese Chamber of Commerce of New York, New York, NY, February 29, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 19)
    - John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, Luncheon, Cambridge, MA, June 28, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 20)
    - Jopling, Michael, British American Parliamentary Group, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, February 2, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 21)
    - Josephson Institute for the Advancement of Ethics, Cambridge, MA and Washington, D.C., 1988 (Box 721, Folder 22)
    - KDKA-TV, Primary Election Night, Pittsburgh, PA, April 26, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 23)
    - Kennedy, Ted, US Senator, Tribute, Cambridge, MA, November 30, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 24)
    - Labson, Mike, Chairman of the Projects Committee, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, October 30, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 25)
    - Lakis, Steve, State Legislative Leaders Foundation, Cambridge, MA, January 12, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 26)
    - Lawyers' Reception for Dick Thornburgh, Lincoln, MA, October 4, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 27)
    - Levi, Edward H., Former US Attorney General, Breakfast, Cambridge, MA, March 8, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 28)
    - Lincoln Club of Orange County, Irvine, CA, March 7, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 29)
    - Lincoln Institute of Land Policy, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, September 20, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 30)
    - Livingston, Congressman Bob, Fundraising Reception, Alexandria, LA, May 22, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 31)
    - Massachusetts Council of Human Service Providers, Luncheon, Boston, MA, November 4, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 32)
    - Massachusetts Republican Party, Essex County Key Club Committee, Breakfast, Danvers, MA, April 20, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 33)
    - Massachusetts Republican Party Leadership, Luncheons, Cambridge, MA, September, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 34)
    - McEnteer, James, Ph.D. Student at the University of Texas, Visit, Cambridge, MA, May 13, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 35)
    - McTigue, Mary, IOP Assistant Director, Reception, Cambridge, MA, October 30, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 36)
    - Middlesex Club, Luncheon, Canton, MA, December 4, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 37)
    - Military Order of the Purple Heart, State Convention, Monroeville, PA, June 19, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 38)
    - Mondale, Walter, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, November 10, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 39)
    - Moolenaar, John, Student, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, February 28, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 40)
    - National Academy of Public Administration, Philadelphia, PA, June 4, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 41)
    - National Academy of Public Administration, Banquet, Washington, D.C., November 20, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 42)
    - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Civil Rights Forum, New York, NY, May 17, 1988 (Box 722, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Counties, Wingspread, WI, November 16, 1987 (Box 722, Folder 2-3)
    - National Association of Regional Councils, Conference, Hartford, CT, May 23, 1988 (Box 722, Folder 4)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education, Leadership Conference, Cambridge, MA, August 8, 1987 (Box 722, Folder 5)
    - National Broadcast Editorial Association, Convention Panelist, Boston, MA, June 20, 1988 (Box 722, Folder 6)
    - National Civic League, Inc., Meetings, Boston, MA, Charlotte, NC, New York, NY, and Washington, D.C., 1987-1988 (Box 722, Folder 7)
    - National Coil Coaters Association, Luncheon, Chicago, IL, October 1, 1987 (Box 722, Folder 8)
    - National Conference on Civic Renewal, National Civic Renewal Project, Boston, MA, November 16, 1987 (Box 722, Folder 9)
    - National Council for Urban Economic Development, Conference, Washington, D.C., April 11, 1988 (Box 722, Folder 10)
    - National Council for Urban Economic Development, Conference, Washington, D.C., April 11, 1988 (Box 722, Folder 11)
    - National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, March 24, 1988 (Box 722, Folder 12)
    - NGA, Federalism Advisory Committee, Meeting, Washington, D.C., March 14, 1988 (Box 722, Folder 13)
    - New England Circle, Discussion Leader, Boston, MA, October 8, 1987 (Box 722, Folder 14)
    - New England Council, Inc., Board of Director's Retreat, Luncheon, Newport, RI, June 20, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 1)
    - New England Council, Inc., Annual Conference, Panelist, Boston, MA, November 19, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 2)
    - New England Mutual Life Insurance Co., Luncheon, Cambridge, MA, October 5, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 3)
    - New England Republican Council, Luncheon, Boston, MA, November 14, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 4)
    - Ohio League of Young Republicans, Luncheon, Dayton, OH, August 1, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania (Eastern Campaign Swing), Speaker for GOP Candidates, Harrisburg, Philadelphia, PA, and Washington, D.C., April 9-11, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 6)
    - PA Governor's School for International Studies, Luncheon, Cambridge, MA, October 29, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 7)
    - PA Manufacturers' Association, Board of Directors, Dinner, Philadelphia, PA, September 28, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 8)
    - PA Manufacturers' Association, Meeting and Luncheon, New York, NY, December 11-12, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 9)
    - PA Republican State Committee, Leadership Conference, Philadelphia, PA, September 26, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 10)
    - PA Society Sons of the Revolution, Centennial Banquet, Philadelphia, PA, March 19, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 11)
    - Peres, Shimon, Foreign Minister of Israel, Guest Speaker, Cambridge, MA, September 21, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 12)
    - Pew Memorial Trust: Funding for the National Organization on Disability (NOD), Philadelphia, PA, June 27, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 13)
    - Polsby, Nelson, Political Science Author and Speaker at Dinner, Cambridge, MA, December 8, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 14)
    - Republican Club of Greater Boston, Guest Speaker, Boston, MA, November 19, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 15)
    - Republican Governors Association, Conference, Sante Fe, NM, November 21-24, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 16)
    - Republican Party of New Mexico, Convention, Fundraising Dinner, Albuquerque, NM, July 8, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 17)
    - Republican Party of Wisconsin, Convention, Banquet, Madison, WI, June 11, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 18)
    - Republican State Committee Spring Dinner, Philadelphia, PA, April 11, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 19)
    - Rostenkowski, Congressman Dan, Breakfast, Cambridge, MA, February 9, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 20)
    - Rotary Club of Pittsburgh, Speaker, Pittsburgh, PA, January 27, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 21)
    - Ryan, Representative Matt, PA Campaign, Delaware County, PA, April 9, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 22)
    - Sawyer, William, Dinner, Boston, MA, May 22, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 23)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur, Former Harvard Graduate and Professor, Albert Schweitzer Chair in the Humanities, City University of New York, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, February 26, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 24)
    - Southern Republican Exchange, Remarks, Columbia, SC, August 22, 1987 (Box 723, Folder 25)
    - Southern Republican Exchange, Background Material, Columbia, SC, January 8, 1988 (Box 723, Folder 26-28)
    - Soviet Initiative Program, Cambridge, MA, September 29, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 1)
    - Suffolk University Law School, Commencement, Boston, MA, June 5, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 2)
    - Super Tuesday, Results, Cambridge, MA, March 9, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 3)
    - Taft Institute for Two-Party Government, Teacher Seminar on American Government and Politics, Luncheon, Maplewood College, Scranton, PA, July 1, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 4)
    - Thiemann, Dean, Harvard Divinity School, Lunch, Cambridge, MA, October 28, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 5)
    - Thornburgh Administration Cabinet, Reunion, Hershey, PA, October 27, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 6)
    - TODAY Show Party, Representing The Rehabilitation Institute, Pittsburgh, PA, ca. May 19, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 7)
    - Toledo Area Governmental Research Association, Joint Lecture Series with the University of Toledo, Luncheon and Evening Addresses, Toledo, OH, November 17, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 8)
    - Union Club of Boston, Luncheon, Boston, MA, June 22, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 9)
    - University of Pittsburgh School of Education, Paul H. Masoner Education Lecturer, Pittsburgh, PA, March 22, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 10)
    - University of Pittsburgh School of Law, Speaker and recipient of Bicentennial Medal of Distinction, February 23, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 11)
    - Verdier, Jim, Harvard University, JFK School, Public Budgeting Class, PA Welfare Reform Budget Initiative, Cambridge, MA, March 23, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Republican Party Leadership Conference, Richmond, VA, June 6, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 13)
    - WTAE-TV General Election Analysis, Pittsburgh, PA, November 3, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 14)
    - Walsh, Jack, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, January 11, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 15)
    - Watson, Will, Wedding, Martha's Vineyard, MA, June 24-26, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 16)
    - West Penn Hospital, Dept of Medicine Annual Dinner, Pittsburgh, PA, June 18, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 17)
    - West Virginia Chapter International Personnel Management Association, Annual Conference, Morgantown, WV, November 2, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 18)
    - "We the People 200," Constitution Day Gala Dinner, Philadelphia, PA, September 17, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 19)
    - Wharton School Graduation, University of PA, Graduation Address, Philadelphia, PA, December 13, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 20)
    - Wheeler, Jack, Radio Show, Ginny Thornburgh's Notes on Program, Cambridge, MA, February 26, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 21)
    - Wirth, Senator Tim, Luncheon, Cambridge, MA, February 8, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 22)
    - Women Executives in State Government, Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, October 6, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 23)
    - World Affairs Council of Boston, Board Member, Boston, MA, June, 1987-June, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 24)
    - World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, Board Member, Pittsburgh, PA, August, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 25)
    - Wurf, Mildred, Trustee of Wurf Fund, Visit, Cambridge, MA, February 29, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 26)
    - York College of Pennsylvania, Commencement, York, PA, May 14, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 27)
  - Schedules, 7.
    These schedule files consist of six folders of Dick Thornburgh's personal schedules from June 1987- June 1988. These files include Mr. Thornburgh's daily, long-range, and monthly schedules, as well as staff meeting agendas. The schedules together with the IOP event files well document the activities and participation of Thornburgh while serving as Director of IOP.
    - Daily Schedules
      - October 5, 1987-December 31, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 28)
      - January, 1988-August, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 29)
    - Long Range Schedules
      - May 31, 1987-November 16, 1987 (Box 724, Folder 30)
      - February 15, 1988-September 5, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 31)
    - Monthly Schedules
      - October, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 32)
    - Staff Meeting Agendas
      - September 2, 1987-August 10, 1988 (Box 724, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 8.
    The correspondence from Mr. Thornburgh's IOP office is labeled incoming and outgoing and is in alphabetical order by last name of sender or addressee. The correspondence covers the year that Mr. Thornburgh was Director of the Institute of Politics, June 1987-July 1988. There is personal correspondence, business correspondence, correspondence related to Harvard University, and correspondence related to his law firm, Kirkpatrick & Lockhart
    - A-K: Incoming and Outgoing, June, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 725, Folder 1-22)
    - Kirkpatrick and Lockhart: Incoming and Outgoing, June, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 726, Folder 1)
    - L-Z: Incoming and Outgoing, June, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 726, Folder 2-26)
  - Clippings and Articles, 9.
    This portion of files from Thornburgh's Directorship of IOP primarily includes news clippings and articles from June 1988-July 1989. There are also occasional reports and subjects such as: judicial reform, budget and the economy, Republicans, "people," and speeches by others.
    These are divided into five sections as follows: First, "General Topics" arranged in alphabetical order, including national as well as Pennsylvania issues; Second, entitled "Thornburgh bashing." Although enjoying the challenges of his new position at Harvard, "Pennsylvania matters did not entirely escape my attention at this time. Governor Casey and his team were seeking to discredit our accomplishments and to focus more attention on their own agenda ... In June 1987, the [Casey] administration undertook a concerted effort, at taxpayers' expense, to document 'deficiencies' incurred during my tenure. Eventually, even the Philadelphia Inquirer took Governor Casey mildly to task. These and other negative reactions finally brought an end to the "Thornburgh bashing" (Evidence, p .198). A goodly number of these articles are annotated by Thornburgh and/or his staff; Third, are "Political Topics" more national in scope including polls, fundraising, Democrats and Republicans, the 1988 Presidential campaign, and candidates such as Dukakis, Reagan, and Bush. Throughout his career Thornburgh followed national politics and issues and habitually kept such clippings; Fourth are the "Republican Rumbles," prepared and distributed by the Pennsylvania Republicans and which effectively covered the political scene in the Commonwealth from May, 1987-July, 1988; Fifth are "IOP articles and clippings" specifically relating to IOP's events and activities and the Director himself. They represent a good overview of the challenges and opportunities for Thornburgh during what unexpectedly was a very brief tenure in Boston.
    - General Topics
      - Abortion, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 1)
      - Books, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 2)
      - Budget and Economy, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 3)
      - Good Government, Management, and Public Service, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 4)
      - International Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 5)
      - Judicial Issues and Merit Selection, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 6)
      - National Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 7)
      - Pennsylvania: annotated articles, clippings and reports, including chapter on Pennsylvania Economy from Osborne book "Economic Competitiveness: The States Take the Lead", 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 8)
      - People, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 9)
      - Philadelphia Convention Center, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 10)
      - Speeches by others, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 11)
    - Thornburgh bashing
      - Thornburgh bashing-articles, June 8, 1987-September 16, 1987 (Box 727, Folder 12)
      - Articles regarding Governor Casey, 1988 (Box 727, Folder 13)
      - Annotated articles regarding Thornburgh Administration Legacy and INC magazine article, July 1987, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 14)
      - Pennsylvania Report, 1987-1988 (Box 727, Folder 15)
      - Articles about Governors Thornburgh and Casey, 1987 (Box 727, Folder 16)
      - Articles about Governors Thornburgh and Casey, 1988 (Box 727, Folder 17)
    - Political Topics
      - Republican State Committee of PA, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 1)
      - GOP PA Fundraising '88 Elections, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 2)
      - Reagan and the White House, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 3)
      - Republicans, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 4)
      - Democrats, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 5)
      - LA Times Poll pre Democratic Convention '88, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 6)
      - 1988 Presidential Campaign (Box 728, Folder 7)
      - Bush articles on background qualifications for presidency, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 8)
      - Dukakis articles about his Governorship and candidacy for president, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 9)
      - Republican Convention, August, 1988 (Box 728, Folder 10)
    - Republican Rumbles
      - May-July, 1987 (Box 728, Folder 11-15)
      - August-October, 1987 (Box 729, Folder 1-5)
      - March, 1988 (Box 729, Folder 6-7)
      - April 5-15, 1988 (Box 729, Folder 8)
      - April 18-29, 1988 (Box 730, Folder 1)
      - May-July, 1988 (Box 730, Folder 2-6)
    - IOP Articles and Clippings
      - January 15-May 28, 1987 (Box 730, Folder 7)
      - June-December, 1987 (Box 730, Folder 8-14)
      - 1988 (Box 730, Folder 15-23)
      - undated (Box 730, Folder 24)
  - Boards and Memberships, 1987-1988; 10.
    After Thornburgh concluded his two terms as Governor in January 1987, a number of opportunities were presented to him in which he could exercise his expertise in the area of law and his vast governmental experience. In this portion of the collection we have, broken down into 13 sections, the various companies and organizations that Thornburgh actively participated in as a member of their respective boards of directors. The companies include: Atlantic Richfield Company (ARCO), Merrill Lynch, and Rite Aid. Academic institutions include: Carnegie Mellon University's School of Urban and Public Affairs (SUPA), University of Pittsburgh's Graduate School of Public and International Affairs (GSPIA), and University of Pittsburgh's Campaign for Third Century. Continuing with his ongoing interest in those with disabilities, Thornburgh held a board of director's position for the National Organization on Disability. The Foundations and other organizations he served include: Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations (ACIR), Princess Grace Foundation, Ronald Reagan Foundation, National Civic League, and the World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh.
    These files are organized in alphabetical order according to organization or company. Within each organization the material is arranged in chronological order. The researcher will find a variety of articles, correspondence, memos, invitations, letters, reports, pamphlets, meeting minutes and notes, and news releases.
    Researchers should note that these "Boards and Memberships" files are related to the IOP files only in that they were produced in the same time period during which Thornburgh was also Director of the Institute of Politics. The same is true with Dick Thornburgh's "K & L" files and the "Ginny Thornburgh at Harvard University" files. Since the time at IOP spans only a year, it is convenient to include these separate yet simultaneously produced materials here.
    - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations (ACIR)
      - Federalism & Balanced budget issues: Correspondence and reports, April, 1987-July 14, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 1)
    - Atlantic Richfield Company (ARCO)
      - ARCO Dedication in France, February, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 2)
      - Atlantic Richfield Company (ARCO) Correspondence and memos to Thornburgh, August-December, 1987 (Box 731, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, memos, and articles, January-August, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 4)
      - ARCO Contributors Committee, December 23,1987-January 20, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 5)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Registration, September, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 6)
      - Board of Directors Meeting, October 21,1987 (Box 731, Folder 7)
      - Board of Directors Meeting, November 18, 1987 (Box 731, Folder 8)
      - Board of Directors Meeting, January 20, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 9)
      - Board of Directors Meeting, February 17, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 10)
      - Annual Stockholders/Board Meeting, April 8-May 12, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 11)
      - Audit Committee Meeting, May 12-July 21, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 12)
      - Executive Compensation Committee, January 20-February 10, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 13)
      - Letter of Resignation to Board, July 25, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 14)
      - General Information Reports, December, 1987-February, 1988 (Box 731, Folder 15)
      - Proxy Statement, January 13, 1989 (Box 731, Folder 16)
    - Carnegie Mellon University School of Urban and Public Affairs (SUPA)
      - Board of Visitors Meeting Materials, September 29-October 20, 1987 (Box 732, Folder 1)
      - SUPA articles, correspondence & pamphlets, January 27-March 21, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 2)
      - Commission on Presidential Debates: correspondence and memos, January 1, 1987-February 18, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations: articles, correspondence, invitations and pamphlets, June 13-August 4, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 4)
    - Merrill Lynch
      - Merrill Lynch news release regarding Thornburgh joining Board & Management Newsletter, December 7-8, 1987 (Box 732, Folder 5)
      - Board Membership requirements, September-December, 1987 (Box 732, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence to Thornburgh (annotated), December, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 7)
      - Memos to Thornburgh (annotated), December, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 8)
      - News Releases, March-July, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 9)
      - Management newsletter and articles, December, 1987-August, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 10)
      - Financial summaries and analyses (annotated), November, 1987-May, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 11)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Issues: forms, reports & memos, April-June, 1988 (Box 732, Folder 12)
      - Board of Directors conference call, December 16, 1987 (Box 732, Folder 13)
      - Merrill Lynch Board of Directors Meeting notes, January 25, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 1)
      - Merrill Lynch Board of Directors Meeting notes, February 22, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 2)
      - Merrill Lynch Board of Directors Meeting notes, April 27, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 3)
      - Merrill Lynch Board of Directors Meeting notes, June 6, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 4)
      - Thornburgh Resignation Letter to Board, July 25, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 5)
      - Proxy Statement, January 3, 1989 (Box 733, Folder 6)
    - National Civic League
      - Correspondence, memos and news releases, November 7, 1986-June 30, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 7)
    - National Organization on Disability
      - Correspondence, January, 1987-August, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 8)
    - Princess Grace Foundation
      - Articles, correspondence, memos and reports, December,1985-February, 1988 (Box 733, Folder 9)
    - Ronald Reagan Foundation
      - Ronald Reagan Presidential Foundation: brochure and itinerary of Thornburgh's visit, April-November, 1987 (Box 734, Folder 1)
    - Rite Aid
      - Articles, annual report, news releases and memos, 1987-1988 (Box 734, Folder 2)
      - Annual Stockholders/Board Meeting material, October 7, 1987 (Box 734, Folder 3)
      - Board Meeting: Financial material and Thornburgh's notes, July 6, 1988 (Box 734, Folder 4)
      - Thornburgh's resignation letter to the Board of Directors, July 25, 1988 (Box 734, Folder 5)
    - University of Pittsburgh Campaign for Third Century
      - Program materials, March, 1988 (Box 734, Folder 6)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Graduate School of Public and International Affairs (GSPIA)
      - Correspondence and memos, March, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 734, Folder 7)
    - World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh
      - Correspondence, memos and reports, March-June, 1987 (Box 734, Folder 8)
    - Letters and Requests to Join